<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Sam on Sam Linville — Product manager &amp; designer</title>
    <link>https://samlinville.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hi, I&#39;m Sam on Sam Linville — Product manager &amp; designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 21:45:52 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://samlinville.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Note on Perfection</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/blog/note-on-perfection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 18:15:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/blog/note-on-perfection/</guid>
      <description>I have been posting content to http://samlinville.com since about 2006, when I was in the sixth grade. Back then, I used a pre-designed template from Microsoft Publisher to post daily blog updates about life in middle school. A year later, armed with a copy of Microsoft Expression Web, I started kicking the tires on HTML and CSS, and a handful of years after that, I used my first CSS framework: Zurb Foundation 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimize for confidence</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/blog/optimize-for-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 13:06:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/blog/optimize-for-confidence/</guid>
      <description>I took on my first internship in 2016 after doing basically zero research on the company. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been more clueless on Day 1, and over my first week, I learned that I was going to be building software for an internal team at a digital ad targeting firm. To be clear, I do not recommend this approach to job hunting&amp;hellip;
In complete honesty, I was immediately disappointed. At the time, I had my heart set on a career in consumer tech and was more than frustrated with myself for eagerly accepting an internship at a company that had so little to do with my future plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backups for the Nerdy and Paranoid</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/blog/backups-for-the-nerdy-and-paranoid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 11:30:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/blog/backups-for-the-nerdy-and-paranoid/</guid>
      <description>In 2017, I had to reinstall macOS on my MacBook Pro. Before taking the plunge, I was careful to back up all of my files, or so I thought. In reality, I neglected the only folder on my computer that actually mattered: An archive of all of my work from design school up that point, carefully sorted by course and semester. I scoured all of my external hard drives and Google Drive folders, and in the end, the only trace of these projects were a few slide decks and thumbnail images from my portfolio site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Code Server on Ubuntu 20.04 with Tailscale</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/blog/install-code-server-on-ubuntu-20-04-with-tailscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 11:25:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/blog/install-code-server-on-ubuntu-20-04-with-tailscale/</guid>
      <description>I wanted the ability to access my development environment from any device, particularly my iPad Pro. To that end, I decided to host an instance of Visual Studio Code on my home &amp;ldquo;server&amp;rdquo; (a computer running Proxmox). Because this dev environment has SSH key access to my Github account and interfaces with various other services, I very explicitly didn&amp;rsquo;t want to expose it directly to the open internet.
As a result, I decided to integrate it into my Tailscale network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kitchen Sink</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/the-kitchen-sink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 16:13:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/the-kitchen-sink/</guid>
      <description>One morning, when Gregor Samsa woke from troubled dreams, he found himself transformed in his bed into a horrible vermin. He lay on his armour-like back, and if he lifted his head a little he could see his brown belly, slightly domed and divided by arches into stiff sections. The bedding was hardly able to cover it and seemed ready to slide off any moment. His many legs, pitifully thin compared with the size of the rest of him, waved about helplessly as he looked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Ethics</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/code-of-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 22:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/code-of-ethics/</guid>
      <description>I believe that you have the right to know how my code honors your privacy and guarantees equal access to all users regardless of ability. In this document, I’ve made every reasonable effort to disclose the mechanics of my website that may affect you and explain my rationale for the way this site is built.
If you think something is missing here, or if you believe I&amp;rsquo;m not adhering to these principles consistently, please reach out to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://samlinville.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 21:45:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://samlinville.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Sam, a product manager and designer. My goal as a design practitioner is to create spaces and tools that make people feel like they&amp;rsquo;re at home, because people who confident in their surroundings and circumstances are happier, stronger people. To this end, I spend a lot of time thinking about how to foster confidence, security, inclusivity, and mastery in the products I build.
At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m at Stanford University getting an MBA at the Graduate School of Business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>